<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Easy on CyberJagadeesh</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/levels/easy/</link><description>Recent content in Easy on CyberJagadeesh</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>CyberJagadeesh</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:28:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/levels/easy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pyrat | THM Writeup</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/pyrat/writeup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:28:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/pyrat/writeup/</guid><description>Introduction Detailed walkthroughs for Pyrat CTF challenges on TryHackMe .
Description Pyrat receives a curious response from an HTTP server, which leads to a potential Python code execution vulnerability. With a cleverly crafted payload, it is possible to gain a shell on the machine. Delving into the directories, the author uncovers a well-known folder that provides a user with access to credentials. A subsequent exploration yields valuable insights into the application&amp;rsquo;s older version.</description></item><item><title>Cheese CTF | THM Writeup</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/cheesectf/writeup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:29:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/cheesectf/writeup/</guid><description>Introduction Detailed walkthroughs for Cheese CTF CTF challenges on TryHackMe .
Initial Foothold echo &amp;#34;10.10.16.91 cheese.thm&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; /etc/hosts Mappped the ip to domain certain-doom.thm.
nmap nmap results Initial scan gives result as lot (n) number of ports open. May be they are tricking us not to look for what we want.
$ nmap cheese.thm -sC -sC -p22,80 Starting Nmap 7.94SVN ( https://nmap.org ) at 2024-09-29 22:48 IST Nmap scan report for cheese.</description></item><item><title>U.A. High School | THM Writeup</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/u.a.highschool/writeup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 22:54:06 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/u.a.highschool/writeup/</guid><description>Introduction Detailed walkthroughs for U.A. High School CTF challenges on TryHackMe .
Summary This CTF challenge required participants to identify and exploit a hidden OS command injection vulnerability in the U.A. Superhero Academy&amp;rsquo;s website. Successful exploitation led to gaining root privileges on the system.
Vulnerability The website contains a hidden functionality that allows for the execution of shell commands. This vulnerability can be exploited to gain unauthorized access to the system.</description></item><item><title>CyberLens CTF |THM Writeup</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/cyberlens/writeup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:32:40 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/cyberlens/writeup/</guid><description>Introduction Detailed walkthrough for CyberLens CTF challenges on TryHackMe .
Tools Used rustscan, ping, burpsuite, nc, metasploit, msfvenom.
Enumeration Lets start the process by mapping host-name to target IP address. mapping cyberlens.thm to the target IP address When any user or application on the system tries to access cyberlens.thm, it will be directed to the IP address specified in the /etc/hosts file. Lets use rustscan for port scanning the target domain.</description></item></channel></rss>