<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on CyberJagadeesh</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on CyberJagadeesh</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>CyberJagadeesh</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:58:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chrome | THM Writeup</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/chrome/writeup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:58:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/chrome/writeup/</guid><description>Introduction Detailed walkthroughs for Chrome CTF challenges on TryHackMe .
Description A password manager is only as strong as the password that encrypts it. You find that a malicious actor extracted something over the network, but what? Help us find out!
1.What is the first password that we find? 2.What is the URL found in the first index? Fully defang the URL 3.What is the password found in the first index?</description></item><item><title>U.A. High School | THM Writeup</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/u.a.highschool/writeup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 22:54:06 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/u.a.highschool/writeup/</guid><description>Introduction Detailed walkthroughs for U.A. High School CTF challenges on TryHackMe .
Summary This CTF challenge required participants to identify and exploit a hidden OS command injection vulnerability in the U.A. Superhero Academy&amp;rsquo;s website. Successful exploitation led to gaining root privileges on the system.
Vulnerability The website contains a hidden functionality that allows for the execution of shell commands. This vulnerability can be exploited to gain unauthorized access to the system.</description></item><item><title>Nessus Installation Guide</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/nessus/writeup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 23:24:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/nessus/writeup/</guid><description>Intro Nessus is a proprietary vulnerability scanner developed by Tenable, Inc. This blog is about the installation of Nessus Essentials on Linux.
Installation Register First lets register in Tenable Nessus Essentials to get the activation code.
Tenable Nessus Essentials Enter your information in the register form shown above, click Get Started.
Download Nessus Mail with Activation Code We should have received a mail with Activation Code. Note down the activation code and click the Download Nessus for the downloading page.</description></item><item><title>Airplane | THM Writeup</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/airplane/writeup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 19:39:14 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/airplane/writeup/</guid><description>Introduction Detailed walkthroughs for Airplane CTF challenges on TryHackMe .
Tools Used rustscan, ffuf, nessus, curl, nc, gdb, ssh-keygen, ssh
Enumeration Lets start the process by mapping host-name to target IP address.
sudo echo &amp;#34;10.10.249.133 airplane.thm&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; /etc/hosts Rustscan Let&amp;rsquo;s start enumaration process using rustscan portscanner.
$ rustscan -a airplane.thm -- -sC -sV Open 10.10.249.133:22 Open 10.10.249.133:6048 Open 10.10.249.133:8000 [~] Starting Script(s) [&amp;gt;] Running script &amp;#34;nmap -vvv -p {{port}} {{ip}} -sC -sV&amp;#34; on ip 10.</description></item><item><title>New York Flankees | THM Writeup</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/thenewyorkflankees/writeup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 07:35:56 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/thenewyorkflankees/writeup/</guid><description>Introduction Detailed walkthrough for New York Flankees CTF challenges on TryHackMe .
Tools Used rustscan, burpsuite
Enumeration Lets start the process by mapping host-name to target IP address.
sudo echo &amp;#34;10.10.140.44 nythm.com&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; /etc/hosts Let&amp;rsquo;s start enumaration process using rustscan portscanner.
rustscan -a nythm.com -- -sC -sV .----. .-. .-. .----..---. .----. .---. .--. .-. .-. | {} }| { } |{ {__ {_ _}{ {__ / ___} / {} \ | `| | | .</description></item><item><title>CyberLens CTF |THM Writeup</title><link>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/cyberlens/writeup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:32:40 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://cyberjagadeesh.github.io/posts/cyberlens/writeup/</guid><description>Introduction Detailed walkthrough for CyberLens CTF challenges on TryHackMe .
Tools Used rustscan, ping, burpsuite, nc, metasploit, msfvenom.
Enumeration Lets start the process by mapping host-name to target IP address. mapping cyberlens.thm to the target IP address When any user or application on the system tries to access cyberlens.thm, it will be directed to the IP address specified in the /etc/hosts file. Lets use rustscan for port scanning the target domain.</description></item></channel></rss>